[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The parallel sides of a trapezoid are 5 inches and 11 inches long. The height of the trapezoid is 4 inches. What is the area of the trapezoid?", "correct_answer": "32 square inches", "incorrect_answers": ["256 inches", "64 square inches", "20 square inches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that starfish can see with the help of the two eyes at the end of each leg?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The student Rosencrantz is coupled with what fellow student?", "correct_answer": "Guildenstern", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamlet", "Waskowitcz", "Rabinowski"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is no cure for this disease that is characterized by the death of muscle cells and tissue. Diagnosis is often based on the results of a muscle biopsy.", "correct_answer": "Muscular dystrophy", "incorrect_answers": ["Scoliosis", "Multiple sclerosis", "Cerebral palsy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What common name is used to denote the dolphin species Sotalia fluviatilis, indigenous to South America?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Tucuxi", "Bufeo gris", "Bufeo negro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Even decades after its summer debut, this Steven Spielberg movie makes some people afraid to go into the water. In what movie does Martin Brody advise, Youre gonna need a bigger boat.?", "correct_answer": "Jaws", "incorrect_answers": ["Titanic", "Overboard", "Dont Go Near the Water"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following Solar System planets are designated as gas planets?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Saturn", "Neptune", "Jupiter and Neptune"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the profession of Mr R.K. Wilson, who was claimed to have taken probably the most famous picture of what was supposed to be the Loch Ness Monster?", "correct_answer": "Surgeon", "incorrect_answers": ["Teacher", "Dentist", "Lawyer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the mouse that helps the cats in The Aristocats?", "correct_answer": "Roquefort", "incorrect_answers": ["CamemBertie", "LEclerc", "Ratatouille"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many prime numbers are smaller than 23?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["0", "11", "12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Portland Alien Museum is dedicated to studying alien life and life forms.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, every Oompa-Loompa is played by the same person.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]